You know, when you talk about sustainability as a culture,
that's a concept I don't think I ever really considered.
Our mothers and our fathers, our grandmothers,
they were living a sustainable life long before sustainability was even a word,
because our cultures, and that's why I'm going to go back to sustainability as a culture,
our cultures understand on a visceral level that we are nature, and nature is God,
and we are connected to this earth whether we want it or not.
We came from this earth and from this earth we will go back to,
okay, or to this earth we will go back to, and that is just that, you know,
and we understand it on a cultural level.
So therefore, culturally, we don't extract from it.
We don't treat it like a foreign object, like a rock that's floating in space,
that we just somehow lend it onto, ready to colonize and extract it.
Even the word colonize, like they're using this word to even talk about them lending on Mars.
Some people want to go colonize Mars right now, okay?